

CONTACT

9 Bhakkar, Punjab Pakistan

+92 3142588002

M mh2588002@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/muhammad -huzaifa-0795142b6/

SKILLS

- AutoCAD
- ❖ MS Office
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- Sketchup
- Revit
- 3ds Max

LANGUAGES

English: Intermediate

Urdu: Fluent

❖ Korean: Basic

MUHAMMAD HUZAIFA

Draftsman | Support Officer

PROFILE

I am a Civil Supervisor, AutoCAD Draftsman and Support Officer with experience in various engineering roles. I started my career at The Engineers and Constructors Pvt Ltd., where I assisted in civil supervisor. Later, I joined Design 19 Pvt Ltd. as an AutoCAD Draftsman, creating detailed interior drawings and planning furniture designs. Later, I joined Habib Bank Limited Pvt Ltd. Engineering Department, working on preparation of B.O.Q., measurement sheets, contractors bill verification, drawings, financial approvals, and vendor management across multiple projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

DRAFTSMAN & SUPPORT OFFICER

Habib Bank Limited - Karachi Feb 2020 - Mar 2024

Contract Under below mentioned companies.

AAA Facility Management Feb 2020 – July 2022 WEMCO Engineering. July 2022 – October 2023 New Khan Company. Nov 2023 – Mar 2024

DRAFTSMAN

Design 19 Pvt Ltd – Karachi Jan 2019 – Dec 2019

CIVIL SUPERVISOR

The Engineers and Constructors. Jul 2018 - Dec 2018

EDUCATION

Diploma of Associate Engineering – Civil 3 years

Govt College of Technology – Bhakkar

2018

Matric - Computer Science

Govt. Model High School – Bhakkar

2015